Hi.
I'm Robert Stewart with Hill13.com.
The next thing we're going to talk about is the lenses on your mask.
Now, depending upon the manufacturer and the features you've added to it, that might or might not affect how you care for it, especially if you're using any kind of anti-fog liners on your goggles.
When you pick the mask up and look on the box it should say whether or not it has the anti-glare finish.
Always remember to use manufacturer-approved cleaners for your mask.
Otherwise, you may damage the coating and defeat the purpose altogether.
Now, if you're using any kind of field mask make sure when you first check your mask out that it's fit and adjusted properly for your face.
This is very important because if it's improperly fitted and you're running, jumping, and diving to the ground; the mask could slip off of your head.
Now should this happen, remember: get low to the ground, keep your face protected until you get your mask back on.
If you can't get your mask on and get clear vision ask a referee to take you from the field.